http://www.niteflirt.com/help/privacy_policy

Phone Sex: Looking for the best phone sex? You've found it, here at NiteFlirt.
Last Revised August 21, 2020
Your privacy and the security of your information is extremely important to us at NiteFlirt. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Niteflirt by sending an email to privacy@niteflirt.com or filling out a Customer Support Form. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information.
This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Service and is incorporated by reference therein. This Privacy Policy covers information you may provide to Niteflirt through the Niteflirt.com website. The Terms of Service, Privacy Policy, NiteFlirt Rules and Affiliate Agreement collectively make up the "NiteFlirt User Agreement" that governs a user's access to and use of NiteFlirt. Capitalized terms not defined herein will have the meanings set forth in the NiteFlirt User Agreement.
Security
Information Niteflirt Collects
Our Disclosure of Your Information
Accessing and Updating your Information
Member Account Cancellation Procedures
Notification of Changes to our Privacy Policy
Security
Niteflirt has certain security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL), which digitally encrypts your information as it is transferred from your computer to Niteflirt. We take the following measures to protect user information once it is received by the Site:
Employees have limited and controlled access to Member information;
Measures have been taken so that servers and the data stored thereon are in a secure physical location;
Security software is used where Niteflirt determines it to be both appropriate and cost effective;
Employees are informed of all security protocol on a regular basis, and
Web security procedures are quality-assured weekly.
Although we strive to keep your personal information secure, no security measures are absolute and fool-proof and there is always a possibility that a security breach could occur, resulting in the release of a Member's data or information.
Back to top
Information Niteflirt collects and how we use it
Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a smooth and efficient experience while you're using the Site and to keep you informed of opportunities available on NiteFlirt. This allows us to provide services and features that are designed to meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier and quicker. We never sell, rent, or lease your information to anyone. We will only share limited information with third-party partners, as described below, to help us enhance your experience using NiteFlirt.
Entry to this Site requires age verification. Niteflirt requires all Members and users to be at least eighteen (18) years old to use any area of the Niteflirt Site and requires all Members and users agree to the Terms of Service. Children are not eligible to use Niteflirt and we ask that minors under the age of eighteen (18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you become aware that a child under 18 has created a NiteFlirt account and provided NiteFlirt with personal information, please
let us know.
When you join Niteflirt using our online registration form, or by registering over the phone, we may collect your email address, Member name, real name, password, phone number and other personal information listed in the registration form. Your Member name is used throughout Niteflirt to identify you to other Members. Therefore, you should be aware that if you use your real name as your Member name, this information will be visible to others who visit the Site.
Your password is encrypted and only used to provide your access to your account. However, we suggest that you use a unique password for each site you use and each account on that site. In the event that one password is compromised, the others will be safe.
Because we connect Members by telephone, we require you to enter a valid telephone number to connect with other Members through Niteflirt. At no time will we share your telephone number with any other Members with whom you communicate. Because Niteflirt initiates all calls, other Members cannot see your telephone number—not even with Caller ID. Although the Niteflirt system maintains the connection between the two parties, we do not monitor or record the content of any calls. However, we reserve the right to monitor or record calls if mandated by law.
We may use your email to contact you regarding account activities, new product offerings and communications relevant to your use of Niteflirt. If you do not wish to receive such communications from Niteflirt you have the ability to stop receiving these mail communications by filling out a
Customer Support Form or by unchecking the box on the My Personal Info Page, which asks if you wish to receive such mailings.
You will, however, always receive administrative emails from Niteflirt that are related to the usage and functionality of Niteflirt. You may not opt-out of these administrative emails unless you cancel your membership.
If you are a Flirt using Flirt Services on Niteflirt, we collect additional information from you so we can process and remit to you your funds and/or verify your personal information. We collect your mailing address and your bank account information to remit payments. We collect your Federal Tax ID (Social Security number or Employer Identification Number) to prepare Form 1099-K if necessary and to help us verify your identity. Members who are not United States taxpayers will not be asked for their Federal Tax ID, though they may need to report income to their local tax authority and may be required to provide equivalent evidence of their identity.
Niteflirt may collect credit card information when you create a Flirt account to use Flirt Services, add money to your Member account or use your credit card to take advantage of special promotions. Niteflirt uses a third-party to process credit cards for billing purposes. This third-party may store or retain a Member's personally identifiable information. In certain cases, we will also use credit card information to help us verify your identity. We do not charge or bill the credit card when we collect credit card information for identity verification purposes.
You may also provide Niteflirt with additional profile information (such as experience, affiliations, schedule, etc.) that is displayed publicly on the Site, on your profile page or in your listings. Other than the profile information submitted by our Members, and except as noted herein, Niteflirt does not disclose any personally identifying information to other Members without your permission. If you choose to use Niteflirt forums know that any personally identifiable information that you post can be read, collected, or used by others, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information that you provide in these Niteflirt forums.
Niteflirt's Tell a Friend Program allows Members to earn money by referring their friends to our Site. The third-party contact information you enter as part of Niteflirt's Tell a Friend program will be used only to personalize a one-time referral email sent to your friends.
Niteflirt may contain links to other sites. Niteflirt is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage you to review the policies of these sites.
Niteflirt also facilitates communication among Members through our on-site Mail and Chat systems. Messages sent via Mail and Chat are identified only by your Member name.
Niteflirt may use certain information collected from our Members in aggregate form to tailor our Members' experience on the Site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences.
NiteFlirt uses a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of this Site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Site. Niteflirt uses the information collected from Google Analytics only to improve Members’ experience with the Site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit Niteflirt, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.
Niteflirt uses cookies. Cookies are small amounts of data sent to a user's browser from the Niteflirt web servers and stored on a user's computer's hard drive. Niteflirt uses cookies to track the pages on the Site that our users visit. This allows us to collect aggregate information about usage on the Site. Niteflirt may also use cookies to deliver content specific to Members' interests, and to keep track of Members' Member names and passwords so that Members do not have to re-enter them during a session. Sessions are tracked to improve your on-site experience and for us to refine our own marketing programs. If you choose not to accept cookies, you will be unable to use the Site.
NiteFlirt collects Device Information from the devices you use to access NiteFlirt. Such information could include your device type, IP address and browser information. Niteflirt uses your device Information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Generally, Device Information tells us the location from which a person is connecting to us, what service provider the person is using and which parts of the Site the user is visiting. We reserve the right to track Device Information for the purposes of fraud prevention, and we reserve the right to release Device Information addresses to legal authorities, if so compelled.
We use information we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve disputes, identify potential liabilities, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Service. At times, we may look at your Member account information and transaction history to identify problems or resolve disputes.
We also use the personal information we collect to detect and prevent fraudulent activity. We share this information with a third-party service provider to assist us with this effort.
If you send Niteflirt email correspondence, or if other Members or other third parties send us email or other correspondence regarding a particular Member's activities or postings on the Site, Niteflirt may collect such information.
Back to top
Our Disclosure of Your Information.
Except as explicitly stated herein, we do not sell, rent or trade any personally identifiable information to third parties.
Your information is NOT sold, rented, leased to, or shared with third parties for marketing purposes. Niteflirt may disclose your personal information to appropriate authorities and to banks associated with your Member account in order to prevent or report suspected fraud and illegal activities, in order to prevent harm to any persons, or if Niteflirt believes in good faith that the law requires it. In some cases, the government can compel the disclosure of information about you, and Niteflirt will need to comply, in which case you authorize it to do so. You also consent to Niteflirt disclosing information about you in connection with disputes involving other Members, and to actual or potential parties to a lawsuit or action that Niteflirt is or may become involved in, (a) if Niteflirt is required to do so, (b) if Niteflirt reasonably believes that such disclosures will potentially mitigate its liability, or (c) for Niteflirt to enforce its rights. Niteflirt may disclose some personally identifiable information to vendors and third-party service providers in connection with communications and payments to Members and other aspects of operating and promoting Niteflirt's Site and Flirt Services. For example, Niteflirt uses a third-party company to deliver Niteflirt promotions, and we share your email address with this company unless you opt-out of receiving Niteflirt's promotions by unchecking the box on the My Personal Info Page which asks if you wish to receive such mailings.
Back to top
Accessing and Updating your Information
You can review, update and change some of your personally identifiable information—including your email address, telephone number, password and PIN number—by clicking on the My Personal Info Page link on the My Account page. You can review, update or change your address and credit card information by going to the My Account page on the Site, clicking on the link to the Payment Info page. You may correct, update or delete any of your Niteflirt listings by clicking on the My Listings link on the My Account page. You may also request a copy of the personal information we maintain about your account by filling out a
Customer Support Form.
We only keep your personal identifiable information for as long as necessary. In accordance with the EU's General Data Protection Regulation, EU citizens may request their data be deleted by filling out a
Customer Support Form. In some cases, we must retain some information for a limited amount of time after you have requested your information be deleted, as required by law or as necessary for legitimate business purposes.
Back to top
Member Account Cancellation Procedures
If you decide you would like to cancel your Member account on Niteflirt, you will need to do one of the following:
Send us an email — including your Member name and email address — by filling out a
Customer Support Form asking us to cancel.
Back to top
Notification of Changes
We will notify you by email if there is a material change in our privacy practices or policies. We will take commercially reasonable measures to obtain written or active email consent from you if Niteflirt will use the information collected from you in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection. We will also notify you by email and/or a notice in your account the changes in this Privacy Policy thirty (30) days prior to a change and at that time you will be given the opportunity to accept or not accept the changes, or cancel your membership.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site or your dealings with Niteflirt, please contact us.
Email: privacy@niteflirt.com
Mailing Address:
© 2020 NF Entertainment, Inc. All rights reserved.
Flirts are not employees of NiteFlirt. NiteFlirt is for entertainment purposes only.
